{
    "id": "1ee7a554be204f719229003bbecca171",
    "title": "Make, Force, Allow, Let",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "ee3069e3f9594fd0a62eec5f5dd36e0c",
            "title": "Make, Force, Allow, Let",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "They ...................................... me wait outside.",
                    "description": "Made is followed by an infinitive without to.",
                    "answers": [
                        "made",
                        "forced",
                        "allowed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ..................................... me to sign the papers.",
                    "description": "Forced is followed by an infinitive with to.",
                    "answers": [
                        "forced",
                        "made",
                        "allowed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was not ...................................... to visit him.",
                    "description": "Allowed is followed by a to-infinitive. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "allowed",
                        "let"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He .......................................... me to accept the offer.",
                    "description": "Force is followed by an infinitive with to.",
                    "answers": [
                        "made",
                        "forced",
                        "let"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You are not ....................................... to smoke in public places.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "allowed",
                        "made",
                        "let"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Will they .................................... us to wait here?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "allow",
                        "let",
                        "make"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Please ...................................... them come in.",
                    "description": "Let is followed by an infinitive without to.",
                    "answers": [
                        "allow",
                        "let",
                        "force"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was ....................................... to apologize for his mistakes.",
                    "description": "Either made or forced is possible here.",
                    "answers": [
                        "made",
                        "forced",
                        "allowed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She was ............................................... to retract her statements.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "made",
                        "allowed",
                        "forced"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We do not .......................................... people to smoke in the kitchen",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "let",
                        "allow",
                        "make"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I found it difficult to ........................................ myself understood.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "force",
                        "make",
                        "allow"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She was ………………………….. to leave work early.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "allowed",
                        "let"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}